A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants E-G FA732C FA732C
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Grants - E to G
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06490508): SMALL GRANTS AND OTHER ACTIONS RELATED TO THE GENERAL EDUCATION MISSION OF THE DIVISION, 1972 October 01-1973 September 30 (Reel 4370;4371;4372)
    SMALL GRANTS AND OTHER ACTIONS RELATED TO THE GENERAL EDUCATION MISSION OF THE DIVISION
    $41,983.94;$41,983.94
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590017): STUDY MISSION ON COMPREHENSIVE DEVELOPMENT OF THE UNIVERSITY OF CHILE, 1964 October 28-1965 October 27 (Reel 0726;4802)
    STUDY MISSION ON COMPREHENSIVE DEVELOPMENT OF THE UNIVERSITY OF CHILE
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590020): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN EDUCATION FOR BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION IN THE UNITED ARAB REPUBLIC, 1964 November 05-1969 March 18 (Reel 3163;5453)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN EDUCATION FOR BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION IN THE UNITED ARAB REPUBLIC
    Office Of Vice President -Finance & Administration;Middle East and North Africa (Cairo)
    $133,904.00;$133,904.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590032): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN INDIA, 1964 October 01-1966 December 08 (Reel 0926)
    $2,047,969.00;$2,047,969.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590033): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN INDONESIA, 1964 October 01-1965 September 30 (Reel 0856)
    ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN INDONESIA
    $261,000.00;$106,287.26
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590034): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN MALAYSIA, 1964 October 01-1965 September 30 (Reel 0837)
    $190,000.00;$153,433.27
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590035): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN PAKISTAN, 1964 October 01-1966 November 28 (Reel 0880)
    Office Of Vice President -Finance & Administration;Pakistan
    $579,963.00;$579,963.00
    Pakistan; Foundation-Administered Project (FAP); Ford Foundation -- Pakistan
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590036): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN THE PHILIPPINES, 1964 October 01-1965 September 30 (Reel 0820)
    $159,000.00;$130,088.94
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590037): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN KENYA, 1964 October 01-1965 September 30 (Reel 0777)
    $344,000.00;$189,959.55
    Africa, Central; Foundation-Administered Project (FAP)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590038): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN LEBANON, 1964 October 01-1965 September 30 (Reel 0798)
    $284,000.00;$282,530.26
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590039): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN NIGERIA, 1964 October 01-1965 September 30 (Reel 0770;3247)
    $422,000.00;$351,330.11
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590040): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN TUNISIA, 1964 October 01-1965 September 30 (Reel 0780)
    $123,000.00;$81,565.95
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590041): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN TURKEY, 1964 October 01-1966 December 08 (Reel 0809)
    $110,619.00;$110,619.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590042): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN THE UNITED ARAB REPUBLIC, 1964 October 01-1966 December 07 (Reel 0763)
    $201,926.00;$201,926.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590043): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN ARGENTINA AND CHILE, 1964 October 01-1965 September 30 (Reel 0708)
    ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN ARGENTINA AND CHILE
    $381,000.00;$351,037.63
    Chile; Foundation-Administered Project (FAP)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590044): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN BRAZIL, 1964 October 01-1966 December 07 (Reel 0717)
    ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN BRAZIL
    $134,765.00;$134,765.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590045): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN COLOMBIA AND VENEZUELA, 1964 October 01-1965 September 30 (Reel 0727)
    ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN COLOMBIA AND VENEZUELA
    $262,000.00;$243,763.66
    Venezuela; Foundation-Administered Project (FAP)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590046): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN MEXICO AND CENTRAL AMERICO, 1964 October 01-1966 December 07 (Reel 0730)
    ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN MEXICO AND CENTRAL AMERICO
    $186,675.00;$186,675.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590047): ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN PERU, 1964 October 01-1965 September 30 (Reel 0728)
    ADMINISTRATIVE AND PROGRAM EXPENSES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICE IN PERU
    $65,000.00;$64,387.53
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590048): PROGRAM SPECIALIST SERVICES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S PROGRAM IN LATIN AMERICA AND THE CARIBBEAN, 1964 November 01-1968 May 11 (Reel 0739;3428)
    PROGRAM SPECIALIST SERVICES FOR THE FOUNDATION'S PROGRAM IN LATIN AMERICA AND THE CARIBBEAN
    $752,566.00;$752,566.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590097): PROJECT SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN DEVELOPMENT PLANNING AND MANAGEMENT FOR THE MIDDLE EAST AREA OFFICE, 1965 January 27-1978 August 31 (Reel 3098;3099;3384;4944;4967;5840)
    PROJECT SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN DEVELOPMENT PLANNING AND MANAGEMENT FOR THE MIDDLE EAST AREA OFFICE
    Office Of Vice President -Finance & Administration;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon
    $3,855,000.00;$3,855,000.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590101): PROGRAM ACTIVITIES IN EDUCATION AND RESEARCH IN THE MIDDLE EAST AREA OFFICE, 1965 January 28-1980 June 30 (Reel 2533;3384;4063;4064)
    PROGRAM ACTIVITIES IN EDUCATION AND RESEARCH IN THE MIDDLE EAST AREA OFFICE
    Office Of Vice President -Finance & Administration;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon
    $1,295,494.00;$1,295,494.00
    Lesch, Ann M.
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590129): PROGRAM SPECIALIST AND CONSULTANTS ON DEMOGRAPHIC ASSISTANCE IN THE REORGTN. OF THE ALGERIAN SYSTEM OF VITAL STATISTICS, 1965 March 12-1968 February 02 (Reel 5585)
    PROGRAM SPECIALIST AND CONSULTANTS ON DEMOGRAPHIC ASSISTANCE IN THE REORGTN. OF THE ALGERIAN SYSTEM OF VITAL STATISTICS
    $83,200.00;$83,200.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590186): EVALUATION OF OPERATIONS UNDER THE NATIONAL LEGAL AID AND DEFENDER ASSN'S PROGRAM FOR IMPROVEMENT OF DEFENDER SERVICES, 1965 April 28-1970 April 27 (Reel 1521)
    EVALUATION OF OPERATIONS UNDER THE NATIONAL LEGAL AID AND DEFENDER ASSN'S PROGRAM FOR IMPROVEMENT OF DEFENDER SERVICES
    $100,000.00;$27,718.57
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590241): ADVISERS AND CONSULTANTS FOR THE PLANNING AND EVALUATION UNIT DEPARTMENT OF AGRICULTURE, GOVERNMENT OF WEST PAKISTAN, 1965 June 02-1975 September 17 (Reel 3145;3146;5027)
    ADVISERS AND CONSULTANTS FOR THE PLANNING AND EVALUATION UNIT DEPARTMENT OF AGRICULTURE, GOVERNMENT OF WEST PAKISTAN
    $248,628.00;$248,628.00
    Cool, John C.;Havener, Robert D.
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590276): EVALUATION OF THE ADMINISTRATION AND EFFECTS OF THE TOTAL NLADA DEFENDER PROJECT, 1965 June 21-1966 June 20 (Reel 1179)
    EVALUATION OF THE ADMINISTRATION AND EFFECTS OF THE TOTAL NLADA DEFENDER PROJECT
    $200,000.00;$56,135.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590294): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN FAMILY PLANNING AND REPRODUCTIVE PHYSIOLOGY IN THE UNITED ARAB REPUBLIC, 1965 July 07-1971 June 30 (Reel 5588)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN FAMILY PLANNING AND REPRODUCTIVE PHYSIOLOGY IN THE UNITED ARAB REPUBLIC
    $396,000.00;$396,000.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590305): PLANNING EXPENSES FOR THE INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE, 1965 July 30-1968 December 13 (Reel 4528;4930;4931)
    PLANNING EXPENSES FOR THE INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE
    $2,350,000.00;$2,350,000.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590319): EXCHANGE PROGRAM FOR SCIENTISTS AND TECHNICAL OFFICERS FROM MAJOR AGRICULTURAL AND SCIENTIFIC RSCH CENTERS IN W. AFRICA, 1965 August 12-1970 August 12 (Reel 1798;1799;3840;3955)
    EXCHANGE PROGRAM FOR SCIENTISTS AND TECHNICAL OFFICERS FROM MAJOR AGRICULTURAL AND SCIENTIFIC RSCH CENTERS IN W. AFRICA
    $80,000.00;$78,706.87
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590330): SYMPOSIUM ON THE PHYSIOLOGY OF HUMAN REPRODUCTION, 1965 August 19-1966 August 18 (Reel 1018)
    SYMPOSIUM ON THE PHYSIOLOGY OF HUMAN REPRODUCTION
    $40,000.00;$27,828.64
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590338): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS IN PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION AT THE NATIONAL SCHOOL OF ADMINISTRATION IN TUNIS, 1965 August 26-1967 August 25 (Reel 5588)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS IN PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION AT THE NATIONAL SCHOOL OF ADMINISTRATION IN TUNIS
    $50,000.00;$38,002.64
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06590344): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN MAIZE IMPROVEMENT PROGRAM OF THE UNITED ARAB REPUBLIC, 1965 August 30-1968 August 29 (Reel 5588)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN MAIZE IMPROVEMENT PROGRAM OF THE UNITED ARAB REPUBLIC
    $83,400.00;$61,883.49
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690012): PROGRAM SPECIALIST TO ASSIST THE INSTITUTE OF APPLIED MANPOWER RESEARCH IN INDIA, 1965 November 03-1967 November 02 (Reel 0926)
    PROGRAM SPECIALIST TO ASSIST THE INSTITUTE OF APPLIED MANPOWER RESEARCH IN INDIA
    $70,000.00;$27,223.20
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690027): FISCAL YEAR 1966 SUPPORT BUDGETS, 1965 October 01-1968 January 26 (Reel 5179)
    FISCAL YEAR 1966 SUPPORT BUDGETS
    $3,208,601.00;$3,208,601.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690028): FISCAL YEAR 1966 SUPPORT BUDGETS FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICES IN MIDDLE EAST AND AFRICA, 1965 October 01-1968 January 11 (Reel 0759;3247)
    FISCAL YEAR 1966 SUPPORT BUDGETS FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICES IN MIDDLE EAST AND AFRICA
    $1,738,198.00;$1,738,198.00
    Middle East; Foundation-Administered Project (FAP)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690029): FISCAL YEAR 1966 SUPPORT BUDGETS FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICES IN LATIN AMERICA, 1965 October 01-1968 January 18 (Reel 0740)
    FISCAL YEAR 1966 SUPPORT BUDGETS FOR THE FOUNDATION'S OFFICES IN LATIN AMERICA
    $1,418,743.00;$1,418,743.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690084): COMPREHENSIVE INVESTIGATION OF NEEDS AND PROBLEMS RELATING TO THE TEACHING OF ENGLISH IN NIGERIA, 1966 January 06-1974 June 30 (Reel 1911;3840)
    COMPREHENSIVE INVESTIGATION OF NEEDS AND PROBLEMS RELATING TO THE TEACHING OF ENGLISH IN NIGERIA
    $75,000.00;$73,920.60
    Fox, Melvin J.;Gamble, William K.;Skolnick, Betty P.
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690085): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS FOR RESEARCH AND PLANNING FOR URBAN IMPROVEMENT IN NIGERIA, 1966 January 06-1971 September 27 (Reel 1439;1440;3840)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS FOR RESEARCH AND PLANNING FOR URBAN IMPROVEMENT IN NIGERIA
    $207,216.00;$207,216.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690166): PROGRAM SPECIALIST IN THE SOCIAL SCIENCES IN TURKEY, 1966 March 18-1975 December 31 (Reel 3806;4108;5977)
    PROGRAM SPECIALIST IN THE SOCIAL SCIENCES IN TURKEY
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690172): ADVISOR ON RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT FOR THE CENTER OF ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL RESEARCH AT THE UNIVERSITY OF TUNIS, 1966 March 29-1968 March 28 (Reel 1497)
    ADVISOR ON RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT FOR THE CENTER OF ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL RESEARCH AT THE UNIVERSITY OF TUNIS
    $65,000.00;$48,183.74
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690180): STUDY OF THE FEASIBILITY OF A DISCONTINUOUS NATIONAL PARK ALONG THE ATLANTIC COAST, 1966 April 12-1967 July 06 (Reel 1056)
    STUDY OF THE FEASIBILITY OF A DISCONTINUOUS NATIONAL PARK ALONG THE ATLANTIC COAST
    $30,200.00;$30,200.00
    Harrison, Gordon W.
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690208): IDENTIFICATION AND ENCOURAGEMENT OF THE DEVELOPMENT OF NEW EDUCATIONAL PATTERNS FOR URBAN COMMUNITY COLLEGES, 1966 May 13-1970 June 30 (Reel 1495;5205)
    IDENTIFICATION AND ENCOURAGEMENT OF THE DEVELOPMENT OF NEW EDUCATIONAL PATTERNS FOR URBAN COMMUNITY COLLEGES
    $25,000.00;$.00
    Feldman, Marvin J.
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690376): CONSULTING SERVICES IN EDUCATIONAL, FINANCIAL AND PHYSICAL PLANNING FOR THE AMERICAN SCHOOL OF RIO DE JANEIRO, 1966 July 12-1971 June 08 (Reel 1497)
    CONSULTING SERVICES IN EDUCATIONAL, FINANCIAL AND PHYSICAL PLANNING FOR THE AMERICAN SCHOOL OF RIO DE JANEIRO
    $162,500.00;$154,967.53
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690392): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN LIBRARY DEVELOPMENT FOR THE BEIRUT OFFICE, 1966 August 08-1968 August 07 (Reel 1482)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN LIBRARY DEVELOPMENT FOR THE BEIRUT OFFICE
    $70,000.00;$62,730.67
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690400): STUDY OF THE ISSUES AND DEVELOPMENTS IN THE FIELD OF COMMUNICATIONS, 1966 April 01-1972 December 14 (Reel 4125)
    STUDY OF THE ISSUES AND DEVELOPMENTS IN THE FIELD OF COMMUNICATIONS
    $1,040,000.00;$1,040,000.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690404): PLANNING AND EVALUATION STUDIES, 1966 August 18-1971 August 17 (Reel 4339)
    PLANNING AND EVALUATION STUDIES
    $126,981.00;$126,981.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690412): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN ENVIRONMENTAL AND PHYSICAL PLANNING IN THE UNITED ARAB REPUBLIC, 1966 August 22-1968 August 21 (Reel 1490)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN ENVIRONMENTAL AND PHYSICAL PLANNING IN THE UNITED ARAB REPUBLIC
    $140,000.00;$300.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690431): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS ON MANPOWER PLANNING THE GOVERNMENT OF TUNISIA, 1966 September 19-1968 September 18 (Reel 1476;1477;5233;5234)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS ON MANPOWER PLANNING THE GOVERNMENT OF TUNISIA
    $235,500.00;$13,456.71
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690441): THIRD JAPANESE-AMERICAN ROUNDTABLE DISCUSSION TO BE HELD IN WILLIAMSBURG, VIRGINIA, 1966 September 22-1968 March 15 (Reel 0856)
    THIRD JAPANESE-AMERICAN ROUNDTABLE DISCUSSION TO BE HELD IN WILLIAMSBURG, VIRGINIA
    Finkelstein, David J.
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690444): SUPPORT FOR RELOCATION OF ARGENTINE UNIVERSITY PROFESSORS, 1966 September 28-1967 September 27 (Reel 3131;3190;3429;3430;4522)
    SUPPORT FOR RELOCATION OF ARGENTINE UNIVERSITY PROFESSORS
    $200,000.00;$181,268.03
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06690464): MEETING OF GERMAN-AMERICAN CULTURAL LEADERS, 1966 October 18-1967 October 17 (Reel 0694)
    MEETING OF GERMAN-AMERICAN CULTURAL LEADERS
    $14,000.00;$12,209.95
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790001): STUDY OF PAKISTAN'S PLANNING EXPERIENCE, 1966 October 11-1971 April 11 (Reel 1325;4125)
    STUDY OF PAKISTAN'S PLANNING EXPERIENCE
    Edwards, Edgar O.
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790006): FISCAL YEAR 1967 SUPPORT BUDGETS FOR FOUNDATION'S OFFICES IN AP, MEA, AND LAC, 1966 October 01-1969 February 26 (Reel 3248;4572)
    FISCAL YEAR 1967 SUPPORT BUDGETS FOR FOUNDATION'S OFFICES IN AP, MEA, AND LAC
    $7,802,310.00;$7,802,310.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790015): FORESTRY DEVELOPMENT PLANNING IN THE STATE OF MADHYA PRADESH (INDIA), 1966 November 22-1969 November 21 (Reel 0926)
    FORESTRY DEVELOPMENT PLANNING IN THE STATE OF MADHYA PRADESH (INDIA)
    $411,000.00;$.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790021): FISCAL YEAR 1967 SUPPORTING PROJECTS FOR LATIN AMERICA AND THE CARIBBEAN (CONFERENCES), 1966 October 01-1967 September 30 (Reel 3398;4113;4115)
    FISCAL YEAR 1967 SUPPORTING PROJECTS FOR LATIN AMERICA AND THE CARIBBEAN (CONFERENCES)
    $60,000.00;$44,179.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790023): FISCAL YEAR 1967 SUPPORTING PROJECTS FOR LATIN AMERICA AND THE CARRIBBEAN (CONSULTANTS), 1966 October 01-1969 March 06 (Reel 0740)
    FISCAL YEAR 1967 SUPPORTING PROJECTS FOR LATIN AMERICA AND THE CARRIBBEAN (CONSULTANTS)
    $482,573.00;$482,573.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790024): FISCAL YEAR 1967 SUPPORTING PROJECTS FOR LATIN AMERICA AND THE CARIBBEAN (PROGRAM STAFF), 1966 October 01-1969 May 19 (Reel 0740;3428)
    FISCAL YEAR 1967 SUPPORTING PROJECTS FOR LATIN AMERICA AND THE CARIBBEAN (PROGRAM STAFF)
    $1,003,517.00;$1,003,517.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790025): FISCAL YEAR 1967 SUPPORTING PROJECTS FOR LATIN AMERICA AND THE CARIBBEAN (TRAINING ASSOCIATES), 1966 October 01-1969 February 18 (Reel 0740)
    FISCAL YEAR 1967 SUPPORTING PROJECTS FOR LATIN AMERICA AND THE CARIBBEAN (TRAINING ASSOCIATES)
    $69,746.00;$69,746.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790037): ACTIVITIES IN CONNECTION WITH THE TEACHING OF ENGLISH AS A SECOND LANGUAGE IN JAPAN, 1967 January 16-1973 August 31 (Reel 1992)
    ACTIVITIES IN CONNECTION WITH THE TEACHING OF ENGLISH AS A SECOND LANGUAGE IN JAPAN
    $382,000.00;$382,000.00
    Finkelstein, David J.;Quinn, John A.
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790149): PROJECT SPECIALISTS, ADVISORS, AND CONSULTANTS TO WORK ON PROBLEMS OF NEGRO COLLEGES, 1967 March 20-1970 March 18 (Reel 5634)
    PROJECT SPECIALISTS, ADVISORS, AND CONSULTANTS TO WORK ON PROBLEMS OF NEGRO COLLEGES
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790188): SUPPORT OF POLICY-ORIENTED SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH ON RACE AND POVERTY, 1967 April 01-1968 March 31 (Reel 1021)
    SUPPORT OF POLICY-ORIENTED SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH ON RACE AND POVERTY
    $1,000,000.00;$.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790228): PROJECT SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANT IN PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION FOR MOROCCO, 1967 April 25-1969 April 24 (Reel 1318)
    PROJECT SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANT IN PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION FOR MOROCCO
    $80,000.00;$24,932.61
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790232): CONSULTANT AND TECHNICAL SERVICES FOR THE UNIVERSITY OF DELHI INDIA, 1967 April 26-1972 September 30 (Reel 1213;3461)
    CONSULTANT AND TECHNICAL SERVICES FOR THE UNIVERSITY OF DELHI INDIA
    Frodin, Reuben;Quinn, John A.
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790235): EVALUATION BY A PRIVATE CONSULTING FIRM OF THE OPPORTUNITIES INDUSTRIALIZATION CENTER IN PHILADELPHIA, PENNSYLVANIA, 1967 April 28-1968 April 27 (Reel 5637)
    EVALUATION BY A PRIVATE CONSULTING FIRM OF THE OPPORTUNITIES INDUSTRIALIZATION CENTER IN PHILADELPHIA, PENNSYLVANIA
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790263): SURVEY OFFICE IN E. AFRICA COSTS OF COUNTRY STUDY PERSONNEL FIELD DIRECTOR CONNECTED WITH SOCIOLINGUISTIC SURVEY OF E. AFRICA, 1967 May 16-1977 January 22 (Reel 1604;1605;4076)
    SURVEY OFFICE IN E. AFRICA & COSTS OF COUNTRY STUDY PERSONNEL & FIELD DIRECTOR CONNECTED WITH SOCIOLINGUISTIC SURVEY OF E. AFRICA
    Office Of Vice President -Finance & Administration;Eastern Africa (Nairobi)
    $611,820.00;$611,820.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790283): PROJECT SPECIALIST AND CONSULTANTS IN PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION FOR THE HARISCHANDRA MATHUR STATE INSTITUTE OF PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION, 1967 May 25-1969 May 24 (Reel 4936)
    PROJECT SPECIALIST AND CONSULTANTS IN PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION FOR THE HARISCHANDRA MATHUR STATE INSTITUTE OF PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790295): PROGRAM ADVISOR IN THE NATURAL SCIENCES IN TURKEY, 1967 June 09-1969 June 08 (Reel 1833)
    PROGRAM ADVISOR IN THE NATURAL SCIENCES IN TURKEY
    $70,000.00;$.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790300): FISCAL YEAR 1967 TRAVEL AND STUDY AWARDS, 1967 June 14-1967 September 30 (Reel 4339)
    FISCAL YEAR 1967 TRAVEL AND STUDY AWARDS
    Office Of Vice President -Finance & Administration;N.Y.- Unspecified
    $2,878,750.00;$2,878,750.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790301): PROJECT SPECIALIST IN INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS FOR THE SHRI RAM CENTRE FOR INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS IN INDIA, 1967 July 01-1969 June 30 (Reel 1834;3315;3359)
    PROJECT SPECIALIST IN INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS FOR THE SHRI RAM CENTRE FOR INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS IN INDIA
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790362): PROJECT SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN DEVELOPMENT ECONOMICS FOR THE PLANNING COMMISSION (INDIA), 1967 June 29-1974 May 10 (Reel 1994;3314;3315;5205)
    PROJECT SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN DEVELOPMENT ECONOMICS FOR THE PLANNING COMMISSION (INDIA)
    $142,826.00;$142,826.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790430): SUPPORT OF SMALL SCALE ACTIVITIES RELATED TO PROBLEMS OF HIGHER EDUCATION, 1980 March 01-1980 April 30 (Reel 4414;5658;5659;5660)
    SUPPORT OF SMALL SCALE ACTIVITIES RELATED TO PROBLEMS OF HIGHER EDUCATION
    $299.64;$299.64
    Hardy, Gladys Chang
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790439): SUMMER INSTITUTES IN LINGUISTICS AND RESEARCH ON LINGUISTICS AND LANGUAGE TEACHING BY THE YAZIGI INSTITUTE OF LANGUAGES, 1967 July 21-1969 July 20 (Reel 1863;3270)
    SUMMER INSTITUTES IN LINGUISTICS AND RESEARCH ON LINGUISTICS AND LANGUAGE TEACHING BY THE YAZIGI INSTITUTE OF LANGUAGES
    $46,200.00;$43,788.91
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790440): PROJECT SPECIALIST IN PLANT PATHOLOGY, UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES AT BANGALORE, INDIA, 1967 July 21-1969 July 20 (Reel 5026)
    PROJECT SPECIALIST IN PLANT PATHOLOGY, UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES AT BANGALORE, INDIA
    Bunker, Samuel E.;Zeidenstein, George
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790467): STUDY THE ROLE OF HIGHER EDUCATION IN THE DEVELOPMENT OF COUNTRIES IN SOUTHEAST ASIA, 1967 August 08-1970 June 30 (Reel 5654)
    STUDY THE ROLE OF HIGHER EDUCATION IN THE DEVELOPMENT OF COUNTRIES IN SOUTHEAST ASIA
    $52,000.00;$29,668.02
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790519): GRADUATE FELLOWSHIPS IN ECONOMICS AND ADMINISTRATION FOR INDIAN GOVERNMENT OFFICERS, 1967 August 24-1968 August 23 (Reel 4925)
    GRADUATE FELLOWSHIPS IN ECONOMICS AND ADMINISTRATION FOR INDIAN GOVERNMENT OFFICERS
    $55,000.00;$46,509.50
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790523): GRADUATE FELLOWSHIPS FOR UNIVERSITY ADMINISTRATORS AND FACULTY LEADERS IN MEXICO AND CENTRAL AMERICA, 1967 August 18-1969 September 10 (Reel 1869;3307;3308;3309;3310;3348)
    GRADUATE FELLOWSHIPS FOR UNIVERSITY ADMINISTRATORS AND FACULTY LEADERS IN MEXICO AND CENTRAL AMERICA
    Central America; Foundation-Administered Project (FAP)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790535): COMMISSIONING ASSISTANCE IN THE CONTEMPORARY OPERATIC REPERTOIRE PROGRAM, 1967 August 31-1972 July 31 (Reel 1870)
    COMMISSIONING ASSISTANCE IN THE CONTEMPORARY OPERATIC REPERTOIRE PROGRAM
    $175,000.00;$18,800.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790548): STRENGTHENING NEGRO FACULTY AND ADMINISTRATIVE STAFF THROUGH THEIR PARTICIPATION IN PROFESSIONAL ASSOCIATION ACTIVITIES, 1967 September 19-1969 July 28 (Reel 4106)
    STRENGTHENING NEGRO FACULTY AND ADMINISTRATIVE STAFF THROUGH THEIR PARTICIPATION IN PROFESSIONAL ASSOCIATION ACTIVITIES
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (06790565): ADVISORY SERVICE AND OTHER ASSISTANCE FOR A CLERICAL SKILLS CENTER IN INDONESIA, 1967 September 29-1972 September 30 (Reel 1870;1871;4814;5399)